We are back.
The first question in the review exercise
asked which assert method is needed to fulfill
the request on line 8.
We have a value within the list of values,
so we need an assertIn test, which I will
build to replace the comment on line 8.
Secondly, the review exercise asked if the
test would pass or fail.
I hope that you entered the code needed for
the test and then ran the test because, if
you did that as I am doing here, you would
find that the test failed.
The third question asked you to identify the
cause of the failure if one existed.
Vilnius, the capital of Lithuania, has a capital
V in variable a, but is all lowercase in variable
b.
Remember, values are case-sensitive in Python,
so these two values are different, which is
why the test failed.